Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 3 and District 3 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.3
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 3 Locals, 2.
  - Local 308
    - Local 308 Outgoing Correspondence, October 24, 1941-August 9, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 112)
      - Gaul to Emspak Regarding Local 308 Wales Strippit Strikes, April 30, 1947; 15.
      - Gaul to Emspak Regarding Local 308 Rem-Rand Strikes, April 30, 1947; 16.
      - Gaul Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 308 Rem-Rand Strikes and Taft-Hartley, June 27, 1947; 17.
      - Francis Jung to Emspak Regarding Local 308 Officers, January 13, 1942; 18.
    - Local 308 Outgoing Correspondence, May 18, 1940-December 27, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 113)
      - Francis Jung to Julius Emspak Regarding World War II and Airplane, February 1, 1942; 1.
      - Jung to James Matles Regarding Local 308 Richardson Boat Contracts, March 21, 1942; 2.
      - Jung to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Health Care and Safety with June 19, 1942, Conference Report and June 19, 1941, Conference Call, July 17, 1942; 3.
      - Jung to Emspak Regarding Overtime, November 2-7, 1942; 4-5.
      - Jung to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Local 308 Constitution, January 14, 1943; 6.
      - David Lozo to UE Regarding Finances, May 18, 1940; 7.
      - Richard McLellan to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, August 9, 1944; 8.
      - Evelyn Mast to Leo Jandreau Regarding Finances, January 11, 1944; 9.
      - Mast to Emspak Regarding Columbus-McKinnon and National Manufacturing, June 19, 1945; 10.
      - Mast to Emspak Regarding Dues and Columbus-McKinnon Manufacturing, November 27, 1945; 11.
      - Mast to Emspak Regarding Dues, and Taber Instrument and Columbus McKinnon, December 27, 1945; 12.
    - Local 308 Outgoing Correspondence, June 4, 1940- December 29, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 114)
      - James Masters to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 308 Officers, June 4-December 19, 1940; 1-2.
      - Masters to James Carey Regarding Dues and National Labor Relations Board, January 5, 1941; 3.
      - Masters to Carey Regarding National Labor Relations Board, Wages and Rem-Rand, February 12, 1941; 4.
      - Masters Telegram to Carey Regarding NLRB, February 26, 1942; 5.
      - Masters Telegram to James Matles Regarding NLRB, April 19, 1941; 6.
      - Masters to Matles Regarding Richardson Boat, April 22, 1941; 7.
      - Masters Telegram to Matles Regarding Rem-Rand, May 5, 1941; 8.
      - Masters to Emspak Regarding Richardson Boat and Rem-Rand, May 7, 1941; 9.
      - Edith Newland to UE Regarding International Harvester Strike, December 31, 1952; 10.
      - Newland to Emspak Regarding Victor Safe and Dues, June 26, 1953; 11.
      - Chesley O'Bryan to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 10, 1954; 12.
      - O'Bryan Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 308 Auto Wheel Coaster Strikes, September 3, 1954; 13.
      - O'Bryan to Emspak Regarding Local 308 Columbus-McKinnon Strikes, December 7-29, 1955; 14-16.
      - O'Bryan to Michael Jimenez Regarding Local 308 Columbus-McKinnon Strike, 1955; 17.
      - Harold Remier to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 308 Headquarters, October 31, 1944; 18.
      - Evelyn Ross to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 15, 1947-June 4, 1948; 19-20.
      - Ross to Emspak Regarding Dues and Rem-Rand, August 9, 1948; 21.
      - William Townsend to Emspak Regarding Rem-Rand Seperate Charters and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, June 29, 1950; 22.
      - E. H. Zastrow to James Byrnes Regarding Overtime, May 10, 1943; 23.
    - Local 308 Financial Secretary's Monthly Report, June 1940-December 1943 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Local 308 Bonding Form, July 19, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Local 308 Rem-Rand, May 13-December 9, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 117)
      - August Hein to Julius Emspak, May 13, 1940; 1.
      - Emspak to Hein, May 15, 1940; 2.
      - Charter Application, May 18, 1940; 3.
      - Hein to Emspak, May 21, 1940; 4.
      - Hein to James Matles, June 17, 1940; 5.
      - Leo Jandreau to Emspak, December 9, 1940; 6.
    - Local 308 Richard Boat Organization, April 21-June 16, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 118)
      - Charter Application, April 21, 1941; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Willard Bliss, April 28, 1941; 2.
      - Bliss to Emspak, June 16, 1941; 3.
    - Local 308 Finances, June 16-26, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 119)
      - Willard Bliss to Julius Emspak, June 16, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Bliss, June 26, 1941; 2.
    - Local 308 Rem-Rand War Labor Board Case, February 6-August 7, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 120)
      - James Matles Telegram to John Steelman, February 6, 1942; 1.
      - Matles Telegram to Willard Bliss, February 7, 1942; 2.
      - Charles Cooper Telegram to George Kirstein, February 7, 1942; 3.
      - Leo Jandreau to William Davis, February 8, 1942; 4.
      - Bliss to George Kirstein, February 9, 1942; 5.
      - Bliss to Neil Brant, February 11, 1942; 6.
      - Ray to Brant, July 31, 1942; 7.
      - Brant to Bliss, August 4, 1942; 8.
      - Brant to Cooper, August 4, 1942; 9.
      - Brant to Theodore Kheel, August 4, 1942; 10.
      - Brant to Bliss, August 7, 1942; 11.
    - Local 308 Richardson Boat Strikes, February 3-March 14, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 121)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, February 3, 1947; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Emanuel Fried, March 14, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to Leo Jandreau, March 14, 1947; 3.
    - Local 308 Rem-Rand Strike, June 16-July 26, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 122)
      - James Matles to J. H. Rand, June 16, 1947; 1.
      - Ed McGrady Mem to James Matles, June 17, 1947; 2-3.
      - Neil Brant Memo to Matles, June 17, 1947; 4.
      - Draft Agreement, July 26, 1947; 5-6.
    - Local 308 1949 Richardson Boat Strike, March-July 1949 (Box 4, Folder 123)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, March 24, 1949; 1.
      - Michael Jimenez to James Matles, April 1, 1949; 2.
      - Jimenez to Julius Emspak, May 5, 1949; 3.
      - Termination of Strike, July 1949; 4.
    - Local 308 Columbus-McKinnon Strike, February-December 1950 (Box 4, Folder 124)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, February 1950; 1.
      - Report of Strike, December 1950; 2.
    - Local 308 Seperate Charters, June 27-July 19, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 125)
      - Michael Jimenez to Julius Emspak, June 27, 1950; 1.
      - Emspak to Jimenez, June 30, 1950; 2.
      - Emanuel Fried to Emspak, July 7, 1950; 3.
      - Emspak to Fried, July 18, 1950; 4.
      - Fried to Emspak, July 19, 1950; 5.
    - Local 308 IUE Inter-union Rivalry, July 12-18, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 126)
      - Emanuel Fried to Julius Emspak, July 12, 1950; 1.
      - Emspak to Fried, July 18, 1950; 2.
    - Local 308 Dixon Chain, October 31, 1950-January 23, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 127)
      - James Matles Telegram to Frank Allen, October 31, 1950; 1.
      - Matles to Emanuel Fried, October 31, 1950; 2.
      - Matles Telegram to Allen, November 9, 1950; 3.
      - Matles to Fried, November 15, 1950; 4.
      - Michael Jimenez to Matles, May 28, 1951; 5.
      - Matles to Milt Burns, June 1, 1951; 6.
      - Matles to Burns, July 5, 1951; 7.
      - Jimenez to Matles, January 15, 1952; 8.
      - Matles to Ernest DeMaio, January 23, 1952; 9.
    - Local 308 Bonding Claim, May 15-June 2, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 128)
      - David Ratner Memo to Janet, May 15, 1954; 1.
      - Janet Barish to David Rosston, June 2, 1954; 2.
    - Local 308 1955 Columbus-McKinnon Strike, December 7-20, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 129)
      - Chelsey O'Bryan to Julius Emspak, December 7, 1955; 1.
      - Emspak to Michael Jimenez, December 12, 1955; 2.
      - Jimenez to Emspak, December 16, 1955; 3.
      - Jimenez to O'Bryan, December 16, 1955; 4.
      - Jimenez to Emspak, December 20, 1955; 5.
    - Local 308 Correspondence, Notifications, Radio Script, Election Results, Reports and Statement, May 27, 1941-September 7, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 130)
      - Radio Script Regarding Rem-Rand with Memo, May 27, 1941; 1.
      - Ray Klausner to Lyle Cordinier Regarding Dues and Columbus-McKinnon, November 29, 1945; 2.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Rem-Rand, March 5, 1946; 3.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Columbus-McKinnon, May 2, 1946; 4.
      - Local 308 Officers Election Results, December 1946; 5.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Columbus-McKinnon, April 21, 1947; 6.
      - Julius Emspak to Leo Jandreau Regarding Local 308 Wales Strippit Strikes with April 30, 1947, Walter Gaul Letter to Emspak, May 5, 1947; 8.
      - Emspak to Joseph Infante Regarding Dues and Rem-Rand, January 19, 1948; 9.
      - Emmanuel Fried to Emspak Regarding Payne Bed and Spring Strike, January 9, 1952; 10.
      - Chelsey O'Bryan Dues Statement, 1954; 11.
      - Emanuel Fried Report Excerpt Regarding IUE Columbus-McKinnon Inter-union Rivalry, March 15, 1954; 12.
      - Sheridan Creekmore Report Excarpt Regarding Local 308 Auto Wheel Coaster Strikes, September 7, 1954; 13.
      - James Matles to Emspak Regarding Tonawanda, Dues and General Executive Board with November 7, 1947, Earl Hosmer Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, 14.
    - Local 308 RemRand Shop News, December 21, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Local 308 Pamphlets, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 132)
      - CIO Needs Unity, 1948; 1.
      - Which Side Are You On with Cover Letter, 1948; 2.
    - Local 308 Leaflets, April 1941-September 1954 (Box 4, Folder 133)
      - UE Means Pay Increase Regarding Rem-Rand, April 1941; 1.
      - Remmington Rand Workers Regarding Communism and District 50 Inter-union Rivalry, September 13, 1943; 2.
      - Peoples Forum Regarding Factionalism, October 11, 1947; 3.
      - The Lesson to be Learned Regarding Taft-Hartley Affidavits and Goldblatt Department Store Employees, October 1948; 4.
      - Shop Gate Meetings Regarding Anti-communism and Rem-Rand, October 12, 1948; 5.
      - UAW Rand and TH 'Purity' Pay Off in Company-Unionim at P-W Plant Regarding Pratt-Whitney and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, November 15, 1948; 6.
      - Raiding Hurts You Regarding Rem-Rand United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, November 23, 1948; 7.
      - Turkey Regarding United Auto Workers Rem-Rand Inter-union Rivalry, November 24, 1948; 8.
      - UAW Speed up in Syracuse Regarding Rem-Rand, November 30, 1948; 9.
      - We Want Real Wage Increases Regarding Rem-Rand, December 1, 1948; 10.
      - General Membership Meeting Regarding Local 308 Officers Election, December 1, 1948; 11.
      - Beware! Regarding Rem-Rand Speed up and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, December 2, 1948; 12.
      - Rand to Close Syracuse Plant Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, December 7, 1948; 13.
      - Hands Off Regarding Rem-Rand and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, December 16, 1948; 14.
      - To the Workers in the Remmington Rand Plant Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1948; 15.
      - We're Happy Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, 16.
      - This is to Advise You Chelsea O'Bryan Letter Regarding Auto Wheel Coaster, September 1954; 17.
    - Local 308 Newspaper Clippings, March 1940-April 1949 (Box 4, Folder 134)
      - "CIO May be Asked to Protect Elmira Remmington Rand Plant Workers Jobs" The Echo, March 1940; 1.
      - "Rand Employees to Vote May 20" Elmira Ludor Review, May 14, 1942; 2.
      - "A Vote For AFC Machinists is a Home Front Victory Vote" Elmira Ludor Review, May 19, 1942; 3.
      - "Why a Strike at Richardson Boat" Tunawanda Evening News, April 5, 1949; 4.
  - Local 309
    - Local 309 Officers Lists, January 7, 1947-March 18, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 135)
      - Lists, January 7, 1947-April 5, 1954; 1-14.
      - List with January 19, 1955, S. F. Grodecki Letter to Julius Emspak, March 18, 1955; 15.
    - Local 309 Incoming Correspondence, August 2, 1940-November 8, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 136)
      - Neil Brant Telegram to Vern Swartz Regarding Wages, October 12, 1942; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Henry Seastrum Regarding Mailing List, November 8, 1940; 2.
      - Emspak to Seastrum Regarding Finances, February 17, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to Seastrum Regarding Local 309 Jamestown Steel Partition Strikes with Local List, June 5, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Caus Nelson Regarding Finances, July 20, 1944; 5.
      - Emspak to Wallace Nelson Regarding Veterans and Literature, February 23, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak to Nelson Regarding Veterans and Dues, March 20, 1945; 7.
      - Emspak to Slyvester Grodecki Regarding Per Capita, January 19, 1951; 8.
      - Emspak to Howard Moore Regarding Local 309 Jamestown Steel Partition strikes, June 16, 1954; 9.
      - Emspak to Anton Ahlquist Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, August 2, 1956; 10.
      - James Matles to Walker Karlson Regarding Jamestown, August 23, 1943; 11.
      - Matles to Hyes Reichard Regarding Finances, August 5, 1949; 12.
    - Local 309 Outgoing Correspondence, February 5, 1940-July 31, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 137)
      - Anton Ahlquist to James Matles Regarding Dues and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, July 31, 1956; 1.
      - James Boyd to UE Regarding Local 309 Officers, January 8, 1944; 2.
      - Slyvester Grodecki to UE Regarding Local 309 Officers, January 15, 1951; 3.
      - Grodecki to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Unemployment, January 16, 1951; 4.
      - Elinor Hammond to UE Regarding Local 309 Officers, January 1944; 5.
      - Frank Hammond to UE Regarding Local 309 Officers, February 6, 1947; 6.
      - Hammond to UE Regarding Finances, February 18, 1947; 7.
      - ALvan Hoag to UE Regarding Local 309 Officers, February 9, 1942; 8.
      - Walter Karlson to Matles Regarding Political Action, August 2, 1943; 9.
      - Robert Kent to UE Regarding National Strike Fund, January 5, 1953; 10.
      - Howard Moore to UE Regarding International Harvester Strikes, October 30, 1952; 11.
      - Moore Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 309 Jamestown Steel Partition Strikes, May 3, 1954; 12.
      - Moore to Friend Regarding Local 309 Jamestown Steel Partition Strikes, August 1954; 13.
      - Wallace Nelson to UE Regarding Veterans, Dues and Literature, February 1945; 14.
      - Nelson to UE Regarding Local 309 Officers, March 5, 1946; 15.
      - Nelson to Emspak Regarding Local 309 Officers, May 16, 1946; 16.
      - Philip Oberg to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 5, 1940; 17.
      - Henry Soastrom to Emspak Regarding Local 309 Jamestown Steel Partition Strikes and Local 309 Officers, April 22, 1941; 18.
      - Soastrom to Emspak Regarding Local 309 Officers, May 23, 1941; 19.
      - Soastrom to Emspak Regarding Local 309 Jamestown Steel Partition Strikes, May 24, 1941; 20.
      - Soastrom to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 8, 1942; 21.
      - Soastrom to Neil Brant Regarding Local 309 Officers, October 16, 1942; 22.
      - Thoralf Warner to Emspak Regarding Jamestown Steel Partition, October 5, 1940; 23.
      - Tom Watson to UE Regarding Local 309 Officers, April 23, 1947; 24.
    - Local 309 Financial Secretary Monthly Report, January-March 1944 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Local 309 Bonding Form, April 16, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Local 309 Organization, October 5-10, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 140)
      - Willard Bliss to Julius Emspak, October 5, 1940; 1.
      - Charter Application, October 7, 1940; 2.
      - Emspak to Bliss, October 7, 1940; 3.
      - Bliss to Emspak, October 10, 1940; 4.
    - Local 309 War Labor Board Case, February 2-11, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 141)
      - Neil Brant to Harry Shulman, February 2, 1943; 1.
      - Brant to Alvan Hoag, February 11, 1943; 2.
    - Local 309 Staff Expenses, June 24-July 29, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 142)
      - Hayes Reichard to Julius Emspak, June 24, 1949; 1.
      - James Matles to Michael Jimenez, July 1, 1949; 2.
      - Jimenez to Emspak, July 29, 1949; 3.
    - Local 309 Strike, June 16-August 2, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 143)
      - Julius Emspak to Lewis King, June 16, 1954; 1.
      - King to James Matles, July 29, 1954; 2.
      - Matles to King, August 2, 1954; 3.
    - Local 309 Correspondence, April 8, 1943-May 1, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 144)
      - Alvan Hoag to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Members and Watson, April 8, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Willard Bliss Regarding Dues, July 28, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak Secretary to Bliss Regarding Dues, May 1, 1945; 3.
  - Local 310
    - Local 310 Officers Lists, March 18, 1942-July 18, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Local 310 Incoming John Elliot Correspondence, July 2, 1946-November 3, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 146)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Salaried Workers Conference, July 2, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak Regarding Dues, December 26, 1946; 2.
      - Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 15-November 6, 1947; 3-4.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, October 31, 1952; 5.
      - Emspak, October 31, 1952; 6.
      - Emspak Regarding UE Fighting Fund, November 3, 1952; 7.
      - Russ Nixon Regarding Political Action Committee, November 3, 1947; 8.
    - Local 310 Outgoing John Elliot Correspondence, June 7, 1946-November 25, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 147)
      - John Elliot to Joseph Dermody Regarding Salaried WOrkers Conference, June 7, 1946; 1.
      - Elliot to Julius Emspak Regarding Salaried Workers Conference, July 24, 1946; 2.
      - Elliot to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 17-18, 1946; 3-4.
      - Elliot to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 23, 1946; 5.
      - Elliot to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 10-December 10, 1947; 6-9.
      - Elliot to Emspak Regarding Local 320 General Electric Strikes, April 4, 1952; 10.
      - Elliot to Emspak Regarding Finances with Statement, April 14, 1952; 11.
      - Elliot to Emspak Regarding Workmens Comp, October 3, 1952; 12.
      - Elliot to Emspak Regarding Workmens Comp with October 22, 1952, Martin Bradley Letter to Neal Eastman, October 23, 1952; 13.
      - Elliot to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, October 27, 1952; 14.
      - Elliot to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 25, 1952; 15.
      - Elliot to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, January 2, 1952; 16.
    - Local 310 Incoming Correspondence, October 17, 1940-July 21, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 148)
      - Janet Barish to Victor Winzig Regarding Finances, August 23, 1943; 1.
      - William Cahn to Leland Austin Regarding Publicity, February 6, 1947; 2.
      - Cahn to Austin Regarding Radio Broadcasts, March 13, 1947; 3.
      - Cahn to Austin Regarding Wages and Publicity, July 21, 1949; 4.
      - Julius Emspak to Gowell Claset Regarding Finances, October 17, 1940; 5.
      - Emspak to Harold Carpenter Regarding Mailing List, December 10, 1940; 6.
      - Emspak Telegram to Claset Regarding General Electric Collective Bargaining, January 3, 1941; 7.
      - Emspak to Earle Sheen Regarding Finances, January 15, 1941; 8.
      - Emspak to John Sekella Regarding Foreman, May 14, 1941; 9.
      - Emspak to Claset Regarding Grievances, November 10, 1941; 10.
      - Emspak to Claset Regarding Military Conversion, June 2, 1942; 11.
      - Emspak to Hans Granquist Regarding Supplies, May 26, 1942; 12.
      - Emspak to Victor Winzig Regarding Supplies, June 10, 1943; 13.
      - Emspak to Grandquest Regarding Chelmug Foundry Amalgamations, August 2, 1943; 14.
      - Emspak to Winzig Regarding Finances, October 14, 1943; 15.
      - Emspak Telegram to Grandquest Regarding Foundry Workers and War Production Board with June 2, 1944, Joseph Keenan Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald, June 6, 1944; 16.
      - Emspak to Harry Sekella Regarding Finances, July 20, 1944; 17.
      - Emspak to Theresa Spallone Regarding Finances, August 7, 1944; 18.
      - Emspak Secretary to Spallone Regarding Amalgamations, December 12, 1944-January 10, 1945; 19-20.
      - Emspak to Max Pubis, March 9, 1945; 21.
    - Local 310 Incoming Correspondence, December 26, 1940-December 20, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 149)
      - Julius Emspak to Max Pubis Regarding Dues and Veterans, July 10, 1945; 1.
      - Emsak to Irene Martin Regarding Per Capita, January 17, 1947; 2.
      - Empsak to Leland Austin Regarding Broadcasts, May 14, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Robert Pack Regarding Finances and Dues Check-off, January 4, 1950; 4.
      - Emspak to Pack Regarding Dues Check-off, August 28, 1950; 5.
      - Emspak to Pack Regarding Finances and Dues Check-off, September 1, 1950; 6.
      - Emspak to Pack Regarding Finances, September 7, 1950; 7.
      - Emspak to Pack Regarding Per Capita, October 9, 1950; 8.
      - Emspak Telegram to Austin, December 4, 1950; 9.
      - Emspak to Austin Regarding Local 310 Meeting, December 5, 1950; 10.
      - Emspak to Austin Regarding Membership Meeting, December 13, 1950; 11.
      - Emspak to Lewis Smith Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, December 20, 1955; 12.
      - Leo Jandreau to Hans Granquist Regarding War Production Board, August 20, 1943; 13.
      - Jandreau to Granquist, January 14, 1944; 14.
      - Jandreau to Granquist Regarding Overtime and Grievances, January 25, 1944; 15.
      - Michael Jimenez to Joseph Brusso Regarding Staff Members, April 6, 1955; 16.
      - Jimenez to Brusso Regarding Local 310 Dues, December 16, 1955; 17.
      - James Matles to Gowell Claset Regarding Elmira, December 26, 1940; 18.
      - Matles to Claset Regarding Elmira and Staff Members, March 6, 1941; 19.
      - Matles to Victor Winzig Regarding Finances, August 20, 1943; 20.
      - Matles to Brusso Regarding Finances, April 11, 1955; 21.
      - Russ Nixon to Claset Regarding War Production Board with June 10, 1942, W. B. Murphy Letter to Nixon, June 11, 1942; 22.
      - Joseph Turkowski to Dennis Dougherty Regarding Grievances, September 6, 1944; 23.
      - Turkowski Telegram to Dougherty Regarding Grievances, September 1944; 24.
    - Local 310 Outgoing Correspondence, October 14, 1940-May 27, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 150)
      - Leland Austin to Joseph Dermody Regarding Dues, April 19, 1946; 1.
      - Austin to UE Regarding Publicity, February 4, 1947; 2.
      - Austin to William Cahn Regarding Radio Broadcasts, March 7, 1947; 3.
      - Austin to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, April 23, 1948; 4.
      - Austin to UE Regarding Packinghouse Workers Strikes, February 11, 1949; 5.
      - Austin to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and UE Constitutions, October 11, 1949; 6.
      - Austin to Emspak Regarding Finances, September 13, 1950; 7.
      - Austin Telegram to Emspak Regarding Membership Meeting, December 3, 1950; 8.
      - Austin to Emspak Regarding Membership Meeting, December 12, 1950; 9.
      - Austin Telegram to Matles, 10.
      - Joseph Brusso to Matles Regarding Factionalism, Staff Members, and International Association of Machinists and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, April 2, 1955; 11.
      - Brusso Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union rivalry, May 27, 1956; 12.
      - Gowell Claset to Matles Regarding Elmira General Electric, October 14, 1940; 13.
      - Claset Telegram to Emspak Regarding Wages, January 12, 1941; 14.
      - Claset to Matles Regarding Elmira, March 3, 1941; 15.
      - Claset to Emspak Regarding General Electric Contracts, June 12, 1941; 16.
      - Claset to Emspak Regarding Wages, Grievances and Run-away Shops, October 15, 1941; 17.
      - Claset to Emspak Regarding Grievances and Wages, November 6, 1941; 18.
      - Claset to W. R. Burrows Regarding Unemployment and Military Conversion, January 17, 1942; 19.
      - Claset Telegram to Leo Jandreau Regarding General Electric Collective Bargaining, April 25, 1947; 20.
    - Local 310 Outgoing Correspondence, May 16, 1941-December 16, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 151)
      - Gowell Claset to Julius Emspak Regarding Unemployment, Hours and War Conversion, May 23, 1942; 1.